Michael Dombrovski

Full Stack Developer

058-690-7459 | madombrovsky@gmail.com

Github | LinkedIn | portfolio

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in Python and JavaScript based programming. Possess strong skills in React, NodeJS and Python that help emerging tech firms accelerate their product development and achieve market competitiveness. I'm particularly drawn to projects where I can collaborate closely with senior developers, leveraging their expertise to further my own learning and contribute meaningfully to the team's success.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Javascript React NodeJS Express Redux Python Django Java Spring SQL MongoDB PostgreSQL HTML CSS Bootstrap

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Talk to me - Github server | Github client | Demo

App connecting people with an anxiety and people that want to help

- Utilized JSON Web Token and httpOnly cookies to store encrypted authentication token client-side safely.
- Built React app components and routing that allows access to public routes and forbids to private ones.
- Implemented PostgreSQL database with tables for users and all needed entities.
- Tools used: NodeJS, Express, PostgreSQL, JWT, JavaScript, React, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

Build it - Github server | Github client | Demo

App for construction workers and their clients

- Developed a robust Django server utilizing Django-rest-framework library, enabling seamless integration of a built-in admin panel and user-model for efficient management of construction workers, clients and client tasks.
- Implemented JWT authentication for enhanced security, ensuring secure access to the application's functionalities.
- Created a dynamic front-end interface using React, Bootstrap, HTML, and CSS, delivering a user-friendly experience for both construction workers and clients.
- Tools used: Python, Django, Django-rest-framework, PostgreSQL, JWT, JavaScript, React, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS

EXPERIENCE

Career break. 07/2021 - 07/2023

Full Stack Java Developer, Elpisor, Ltd.

Rehovot, Israel. 01/2021 - 07/2021

- Implemented rest controllers to operate with data models to store property objects data.
- Maintained web service in the real estate sphere to find, rent or sell a property.
- Was actively improving the working process offered to implement agile methodology that was then implemented.
- Implemented Swagger to our API that created a page with all API information for our fronted team usage.
- Tools used: microservices, Java, MongoDB, Spring-security, Spring Data, Spring REST controllers

The whole team was let go since the project was closed.

Nurse, National Medical and Surgical Center named after N.I. Pirogov.

Saint Petersburg, Russia. 2010 - 2018

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Tel-Aviv, Israel 07/2023 - 03/2024

Java Development, Web development, Tel-Ran, Educational Center

Haifa, Israel. 10/2019 - 04/2021

Nursing care, Medical college №6

Saint Petersburg, Russia. 09/2007 - 06/2010

Bachelor, Devices and systems of orientation, stabilization, and navigation

Saint Petersburg State University of Aerospace and Instrumentation

Saint Petersburg, Russia 2006 - 2007

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent, Hebrew - Intermediate, Russian - Native.